raceit.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy Policy

Call us today! **866-972-2348**

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Web site and our products and services. Race IT is committed to maintaining the privacy of the clients and potential clients alike. Our relationships with our clients and potential clients are of the utmost importance; the trust we’ve developed with them is a paramount concern of ours. We collect two types of information from users of our Web site: (1) personal information you choose to disclose to us; and (2) aggregate information collected on users of our Web site.

##### Personal Information

You may be requested to provide personal information to us when you register with us, send an e-mail, or submit a résumé for our review. This information is maintained only for its intended use. We do not sell or rent the personal information provided by users of our Web site. If you do not feel comfortable sharing information via our Web site feel free to contact us via regular mail or telephone to submit the same information. Our Web site may contain hyperlinks to sites controlled or maintained by independent third parties. We do not control the use of personal information provided to such third parties and such information will be governed by the applicable third party’s privacy policy.

##### Aggregate Information

We may collect certain information about all users of our Web site such as an Internet Protocol (IP) address, the type of browser and operating system used, the date and time visited, and the pages visited. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information about you and is never distributed to outside parties. This information is captured for our sole usage in learning about our visitors and helping us continually improve your online experience with our firm.

##### Hyperlinks to Third Party Sites

This Web site may contain hyperlinks to third party Web sites. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience for the users of our Web site. Race IT is not responsible for the content on third party sites. Our inclusion of hyperlinks our site does not necessarily imply an endorsement of the linked site or the company that maintains it.

##### General Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about our Web site in general, please contact us as follows: 

Race IT  
4551 Cox Road, Suite 325  
Glen Allen, VA 23060

Phone: l 866-972-2348  
Fax: 804-935-8900
